Macià Dalmau Roig

Digital Content Creator



EXPERIENCE

NGO Partner catcher at Oxfam

2017 - 2018 - Barcelona

Communitcated with all levels of management and staff to establish productive relationships. Ability to explain the differents projects to the clients, listen them to undestand his needs and ability to respond effectively.

Freelance Graphic Designer

2018 - Present - Sant Cugat del Vallès, Barcelona

Designed logos, office stuff and social media content for different companies. Collaborated with product and development teams on projects to improve the product experience.

Instructor at Saló de l'Ensenyament

2021 - Barcelona

Explained the different study programs of CITM to the future students. Instructed on how to play a VR game and use his tools. Answered questions about the degree requirements, academic support sevices, policies and procedures.

EDUCATION

Game Design and Development

Centre de la Imatge i Tecnologia Multimèdia | CITM (UPC)

2018 - Present

Modeling with Cinema 4D

Microgestió Barcelona

2018 - 2019

ABOUT ME

I consider my self an active and creative person, with initiative and a lot of courage.

I always aim to learn new things keeping my positive spirit.

maciadalmau@gmail.com +34 616 542 715

Sant Cugat del Vallès (Barcelona)

Industry Knowledge

Product Design
User Interface
User Experience
Interaction Design
Motion Graphics
Wireframing
Rapid Prototyping
Game Development
Game Design

Tools & Technologies

Figma, After Effects, Photoshop, Illustrator, Unity, Maya, Blender, Visual Studio Code, Github...

Other Skills

Level Design

C++, C#, HTML

Languages

Catalan (native)
Spanish (native)
English (professionnal)

Social

maciadalmau.com
linkedin.com/in/maciadalmau